<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolios on Cecilia Gomes</title>
    <link>https://Ceici92.github.io/CeciliasPortofolio/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Portfolios on Cecilia Gomes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 14:28:25 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Ceici92.github.io/CeciliasPortofolio/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Street AR</title>
      <link>https://Ceici92.github.io/CeciliasPortofolio/portfolio/streetar/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 14:28:25 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Ceici92.github.io/CeciliasPortofolio/portfolio/streetar/</guid>
      <description>As a transversal project during my master 2 in Virtual and Augmented Reality, I created an AR application dedicated to one fresco.
   We decided to make an AR application in connection with art, and we took advantage of this magnific fresco painted by students of our school, children of several activity centre in Evry, and the street artist Vince. The creation of the fresco was an excuse to begin a dialogue around art and the environment, between the students and the children.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customers&#39; Dashboards</title>
      <link>https://Ceici92.github.io/CeciliasPortofolio/portfolio/arteria/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 10:11:02 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Ceici92.github.io/CeciliasPortofolio/portfolio/arteria/</guid>
      <description>The company:  Between my first and second year at Telecom SudParis I made an internship of two month at Arteria, a subsidiary of RTE. This start-up of 15 employees aim to make profitable the infrastructures of RTE, by rehabilitating electrical pylons, and deploying optical fibers and an IoT (Internet of Things) network.
 My mission:  For my internship, I integrated a team of 4 people dedicated to provide connected sensors, connectivity and a web interface to farmerss and small cities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virtual Visit of a Genopole</title>
      <link>https://Ceici92.github.io/CeciliasPortofolio/portfolio/genopole/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 10:55:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Ceici92.github.io/CeciliasPortofolio/portfolio/genopole/</guid>
      <description>Evry&amp;rsquo;s Genopole is a bioparc dedicated to biotechnologies, divided in 5 campuses, where research laboratories, companies and a hospital are spread. To enable researchers or entrepreneurs to visualise the bioparc at distance, the employees of the Genopole wanted to enable a visit of the campuses in Virtual Reality. Alongside two colleagues, we decided to take part in this project during our 2nd year at the engineering school Telecom SudParis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cultural Platform &amp; Interactive Visits</title>
      <link>https://Ceici92.github.io/CeciliasPortofolio/portfolio/entrepreneurchallenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 19:46:48 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Ceici92.github.io/CeciliasPortofolio/portfolio/entrepreneurchallenge/</guid>
      <description>During my second year at the engineering school Telecom SudParis, I took part in the &amp;ldquo;Entrepreneur Challenge&amp;rdquo; organized by the start-up incubator.
In a team of six, we had one week to imagine an innovative start-up, and to produce a fifteen-page document describing: the problem our start-up would answer, its market, its competitors, the marketing and commercial plan, its implementation, the organisation of its launching, and financial elements.
Below, I describe some steps of the reflexion around the start-up.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
